Teenage snack!
Roadkill is a horror, thriller, tv movie film directed by Johannes Roberts.
Six young friends on a road trip in Ireland run afoul of gypsies who
curse them for accidentally running down an old woman.
The curse takes the form of a terrifying flying
beast that tries killing them all.
Kate, played by Kacey Barnfield.
Seamus, played by Stephen Rea.
Hailey, played by Eliza Bennett.
Ryan, played by Oliver James.
Luca, played by Ned Dennehy.
Chuck, played by Diarmuid Noyes.
Roadkill is a 2011 American television horror film directed by
Johannes Roberts and written by Rick Suvalle.
It stars Kacey Barnfield, Oliver James, Diarmuid Noyes and Stephen Rea.
It is the twenty-fifth film in the Maneater film series.
Roadkill premiered on Syfy on April 23, 2011, and was
released on DVD on August 30, 2011.
The tone is dark and intense.